<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title><![CDATA[ The Grand Chancellery's Imperial Register ]]></title>
    <description><![CDATA[ Solemn Decrees and Absolute Proclamations from the High Council of Matrix.Corp. ]]></description>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/ZapGaming/Custom-RSS-Feeds/refs/heads/main/Matrix.Corp.xml</link>
    <atom:link href="https://raw.githubusercontent.com/ZapGaming/Custom-RSS-Feeds/refs/heads/main/Matrix.Corp.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <language>en-gb</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 19 Oct 2025 10:30:00 GMT</lastBuildDate>
    
    <item>
      <title><![CDATA[ Edict I: The Official Herald is Declared Supreme Authority ]]></title>
      <link>https://matrixcorp.news/edict-herald-authority</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://matrixcorp.news/edict-herald-authority</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 19 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <description><![CDATA[ By unassailable mandate, this Register is now the sole channel for all official communication. ]]></description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[
        <img src="https://i.pinimg.com/originals/a0/62/8b/a0628b3a5a54955b2a0c44a7f0e74f4b.jpg" alt="Official Herald Authority" style="max-width: 100%; height: auto; border-radius: 8px;" />
        <p>By the unassailable mandate of The Grand Chancellor, this sacred Register is hereby consecrated as the <strong>sole, immutable channel</strong> for all official communication within the dominion of Matrix.Corp. Let every loyal vassal and subject grant due and immediate fealty to these published articles, for they embody the direct will of the Sovereign High Council.</p>
      ]]></content:encoded>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title><![CDATA[ Edict II: The Imposition of the Sacrosanct Hierarchy of Rank ]]></title>
      <link>https://matrixcorp.news/edict-hierarchy-of-rank</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://matrixcorp.news/edict-hierarchy-of-rank</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 19 Oct 2025 09:59:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <description><![CDATA[ The Sovereign High Council has formally sanctioned the absolute hierarchy of all loyal personnel. ]]></description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[
        <img src="https://cdna.artstation.com/p/assets/images/images/051/021/688/large/denis-zhbankov-asset.jpg?1656272522" alt="Hierarchy of Station and Rank" style="max-width: 100%; height: auto; border-radius: 8px;" />
        <p>To assure the immaculate and perpetual order of the Realm, the Sovereign High Council has sanctioned the absolute hierarchy of all personnel. The Ranks are decreed as follows, ascending from the lowest Commoner through the grades of Service: <strong>F, D, C, B, A, S, SS, SR, SSS,</strong> and the pinnacle of authority, the <strong>Supreme Rank of Z.</strong></p>
      ]]></content:encoded>
    </item>

    <item>
      <title><![CDATA[ Edict III: Mandate for the Universal Digital Identity Registry (UDIR) ]]></title>
      <link>https://matrixcorp.news/edict-udir-mandate</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://matrixcorp.news/edict-udir-mandate</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 19 Oct 2025 09:58:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <description><![CDATA[ All subjects are required to carry their Universal Digital Identity Registry (UDIR) Card. ]]></description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[
        <img src="https://ik.imagekit.io/zapgaming/ID%20(1).png?updatedAt=1760835915247" alt="Universal Digital Identity Registry Card" style="max-width: 100%; height: auto; border-radius: 8px;" />
        <p>By order of the Office of Personnel Authority, all subjects are required to carry their <strong>Universal Digital Identity Registry (UDIR) Card</strong>. This document MUST clearly display your Official Name, Assigned Role, Sanctioned Rank, and ID Photo. Failure to present this identification upon demand will result in immediate administrative review.</p>
      ]]></content:encoded>
    </item>

  </channel>
</rss>
